hipmomsgogreen.com 2014-06-18

# Privacy Policy | Hip Moms Go Green

Welcome to Hip Moms Go Green Internet website and online magazine. At Hip Moms Go Green. We value and protect your privacy and strive to earn your continued respect, loyalty and trust. We want you to know that the information that you share with us will be treated with care and consideration for your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to disclose and explain and permit you to understand how we collect, use, and protect the confidentiality of personal information collected from you by way of this website.

**Collecting and Using Personal Information**

Hip Moms Go Green requires no personal information for access to our site and will collect information from you on a strictly voluntary basis. You may choose to receive E-Mail updates from us upon request and may at any time ask to discontinue receiving them.

When you visit our website, and when you communicate with us via our site, we will, at this time, collect only your e-mail address.

We will not sell, license or transfer personal information we gather from you except as may be necessary to provide you with information, services or products that we offer independently or jointly with others.

Hip Moms Go Green may use your e-mail address to advise you of promotions, updates and special offers we think may be of interest to you and to send you regularly scheduled E-Mail Magazine Subscriptions.

**Confidentiality of Personal Information**

Hip Moms Go Green uses reasonable efforts and precautions to keep all information obtained from our on-line visitors secure against unauthorized access and protect the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information. Hip Moms Go Green uses appropriate security controls and processes to secure and protect your privacy.

**Information, Contests, Promotions, or Other Offers**

We may from time to time, send you information or offers regarding products or services of Hip Moms Go Green or others in which we believe you might be interested.

If you have Opted-In to receive the Hip Moms Go Green E-Mail online Magazine, but decide that you no longer wish to subscribe, you are instructed to follow the instructions located at the end of the Hip Moms Go Green-E-Mail messages in order to Opt –Out.

**Third Party Links**

Hip Moms Go Green provides links to other websites. Please be aware that once you leave our website and enter another website, you may be subject to different privacy practices and policies over which Hip Moms Go Green has no control and for which Hip Moms Go Green is not responsible. Please use prudence in utilizing such links and in disclosing any personal information on those sites.

**Effective Date, Intent and Notice**

The foregoing Privacy Policy is effective as of November 30, 2009. Hip Moms Go Green may change this statement periodically without notice. Changes to our Privacy Policy will be noted here so that you can be informed about the privacy protections we provide. This statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

By visiting Hip Moms Go Green, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of Hip Moms Go Green after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on Hip Moms Go Green will constitute your acceptance of those changes.

© 2009. All Rights reserved
